はい。
今日は
コブクロのカバンの中身
なんかだんだん
このYouTubeも慣れてきたね。
そうですね。
慣れてきたね？
ね？
楽しくなってきたね。
僕もこれから職業欄には
もう入れてる、入れ、
それ言うと
ほんまにWikipediaに書かれんねんから。
YouTuberで。
俺はもうYouTuberやで。
まあ、やってる時点で。
そうすね。
今日はえと
カバンの中身って言うやつ
これはよくね、テレビとかでやりますよね。
ね？
こんな事俺らがやる日が来るなんて
ぶっちゃけさ
この話あったんじゃないですか？過去
カバンの中身にしてください、みたいな
テレビからのオファー
余裕で無しにしてたんですけど
今まで１００回ぐらい無しにしたんで
なんで余裕で
この話、この話な？
YouTubeのその、考えやってくれたはる人とか
今度どうですかって言われた時
オッケした時
スタッフがびっくりしたもんな
あんだけとこ割ってさ
そう。
黒田さんのYouTubeのハードル
低いねん。
YouTube、こんだけ本気でやるねんて言う
これもオッケーだと言う
へーじゃー
小渕さん
ほんまでリアルなやつでいいですか？
これ僕がいつも持っているカバン。
小渕バック。
あの、黒田さんも
これ、パッと片手でちょっと持って
片手で
パッと持って
パッと持って。
腰可笑しいなるわお前
もう、これは日常です。
小渕さんはほんま
もう、そのままですね。
もう、荷物は多い。
はい、これは当たり前の
パソコンね。
これは歌詞、メモ、全部、音楽が
デスクトップは見せられないですけど
何が何か分からへんぐらい
１００ぐらいアイコンがあるんですよ。
そう。物凄いです。
ぐちゃぐちゃなってます。
へーまー
パソコンの電源。
充電。
もうこれが
あるんですね？
はい、はい。
ま、最近やとちょっと
カメラを買いました。
なんのカメラを？
これはもすげーの。
あの。。。。
コンデジの中でも
このCanon G5X
小渕さんのさ
その
小渕さんの
これも三脚も付いてんねや。
あ、すごいね。
付いてないねん。
付けとんねん。
あ、付けとるんねん。
すごいね。
これ工夫よ。
もう同棲お前
こんなもん、もう一か月もたったもうつかいへんなるやん。
うるさいねんお前は。
まま
マスクですね？
あ、マスク入れ？
うん。
マスク入れはいつもこれに入れてたり
とか
ま、当然ですけど
さくいんばこ？？？
財布
財布がもう
お前もう松方ひろきさんやもんな。
元々
いややや
開けへん、開けへんけど
何これ？
もう怖いもん。
怖い。
開けんも怖い。
開けへん！
開けへん！けどもう
すごいよ、なんか。
いやいや。
こ言うもんやん
長財布って言うんのは
いや、や、や。
それから
あ、お茶ね。
いや。お前さ。。。
お前これさ。。。
たかはしMary June さんが同じの飲んでんで。
お前、あずき美人ちゃのこと言うな！
これ何年飲んでるんと思ったのか？
お前が飲んでるんのは
モデルさんとおんなじもんやねん。
あら。
なんでそんなもんばっかり入ってるんだお前？
当たり前やろん。
ちょっと俺ドキドキしてるもん。
顔グリグリするやつが出てくるかも。
出てへん、出てへん。
ま、ま、あとはもう
サングラスを入れてたりとか
ちょっと、ま、アクセサリー、現場で使うやつ入れてるでしょう？
早いね。
ま、でもこんな、みんな
香水ちょっと入れて
いイェ。。。
瓶で？
小分けしてへんの？
瓶で。
瓶で？？
瓶で持ってくの？！お前？
すげーな。
瓶で。
すごいね。
これがあるから、ほら？
安全やからさ。
このかちゃってするやつ。
これ飛行機行けるの？
あの、
大きのに入れ時もあるけど
ま、大きとかちっさいとか話からへんけど
あとは、ま、ま
充電器とか
もいっぱいね。
これ、あの、なんつ言うの？
イヤホン。
あ、これ。
これ！
これめちゃくちゃ便利ですよ。
USB一個からさ
USB-C, Lightning...
あの
全部出てるねんこれ。
４んもあったから
俺も小っちゃいの持ってるもん。
なんだそれや。
今日これ俺一番自慢しおうっと思って
持たんや。
俺のやつは
ここの、この、入り口をキュッキュッキュっと
で三つ、入れ替えれんか。
これはさぁ
四つ
四代充電できるの？
そう。
だから
スピードは４分の１やねん。
あかんやん。
でも四つ行けるのよ？
お、そうそうそう。
すごいゆとりがある時に
これは俺が使うん。
ゆとりがある時。。。
あ！あとこれはね
携帯空気清浄機。
出た。。。
え？
なんで、みんなつけてるんやろ？
これ、Takahashi Mary Juneさんも同じもん持ってるんだぞ。
いちり、あの
一分間で
浄化する空気が
これの周りだけ、浄化した。
お前さぁ。。。
My surroundings are
Hey, stop that.
You're going to stop using that,
pretty soon.
Inside, there's a small purple light.
Everyone probably thinks this is a joke.
This is the reality.
This guy always has things like that in his bag.
The rest is,
now I'm doing things like writing some lyrics.
And books I want to read, right?
But they're in your computer.
No, no.
The thing about books is,
if it's not a book, I can't.
These kinds of books I really like.
(?) Things like "searching for words"
This is amazing.
This is a bit of that, right?
Kobuchi.
You just added these to look cool.
No, no, no!
I actually put these in.
You totally added these to your bag just for coolness, didn't you?
In your bag?
A little bit for coolness right?
A little...
I'm writing a little lyrics,
I wanted to show these, right?
Because, this is almost
unused.
It feels like it was never opened, right?
Stop it.
Today is a YouTube recording,
so I brought them.
The next is, well,
headphones.
Yes, this is, you know,
Hey, you know,
You already have earphones,
why do you need headphones?
This is what Neumann released.
Oh, is it?
Neumann released this.
Wow.
This, recently I've been using this very much.
This.
(?) Super topic.
Right?
Well even afterwards,
it's like that.
Ah, the next is, well,
earphones, right?
How many earphones do you have?
You have 3 that seem the same though.
No.
A weird person who use these while on the move.
If on the move, I use these.
When do you use this?
This?
This is when I run, for example.
Ah,
there's already 3 in here.
One is enough,
just one.
Well the rest is, already,
that right?
Cough drops I always suck on.
Chapstick, right?
And next,
throat spray.
Something like Cemedine.
This is for your nose.
For pollen, those things you wear on your nose.
???
A little supplements, for example.
That's that.
???
is the most
(?) the clatter of the main topic of today, right?
You didn't bring but,
(?) The clatter, this
about 4 times the amount here, right?
Already, about the amount of one person living alone.
Like the same.
Yes.
Let's spread this all out.
Yes. Oh these? Everything.
Kobuchi's stuff.
I'm so good at lining these up.
Like lining stuff up, or
when writing on the blackboard
you're really good at, but,
the inside of your bag is extremely messy.
Why? I wonder.
You ask, but,
how do I clean up the inside of my bag?
How?
This is a different skill, right?
How do I clean the inside of my bag?
Because, there are no divisions.
So, I'll say one thing.
You don't need all this.
No... I need it.
Computer, and,
this charger, and
wallet,
and then
you only need one, either earphones or headphones.
I don't like that...
You also don't need a camera anymore.
なんて???しいな
Not needed.
I need it, I need it.
I definitely need this.
Yes.
But this is actually,
my,
a bit.
But really,
this is it.
Yes.
This was the inside of my bag.
Next time.
I always bring this around.
Actually,
this is the first time I-
(?)いごえる Boku-note
Inside Kobukuro Kuroda's bag.